https://www.stonewallcable.com/privacy

Select the Project You Wish to Add this Product to:
Main
or Create a new Project:
Core Capabilities
Welcome to Stonewall Cable!
Log In
Stonewall Cable, Inc.
STU-III / STE
KIV-7M Red to RS-530 DTE (DB25F)
*SC-4032-a Customize
KIV-7M Red (VHDCI68) to RS-530 DTE (DB25F); Choose Any Length, and Jacket (Standard PVC, Fire Rated Plenum, or Low Smoke Zero Halogen)
KIV-7M Black to RS-530 DCE (DB25M)
*SC-4033-a Customize
KIV-7M Black (VHDCI68) to RS-530 DCE (DB25M); Choose Any Length, and Jacket (Standard PVC, Fire Rated Plenum, or Low Smoke Zero Halogen)
*F50G-D Customize
Duplex OM3 Multimode 50/125 10 Gig Laser Optimized Fiber Cable;
Choose Color, Jacket Type (Riser, Plenum or LSZH), Connectors and Optional Pulling Eye. Available in Any Length!
OM4 Multimode 50/125 10/40/100 Gig 4-Strand Fiber Cable
*FOM4-AZ Customize
4-Strand OM4 Multimode 50/125 10/40/100 Gig Laser Optimized Fiber Distribution Cable with Furcation Tubing; Choose Connectors, Jacket Type, and Optional Pulling Eye. Available in Any Length!
More >
Military & Tactical
Network
Category 5e UTP/STP Cable & Components
Category 6 UTP/STP Cable & Components
Category 6a UTP/STP Cable & Components
Coaxial
DS0 / DS1
RJ21 / RJ21 Hydra
T1
Telco50
Telco64
RJ21 Cable - Category 5e Telco 50 Male / Telco 50 Female
*SC-3068-2bcd Customize
RJ21 Cat5e Cable 25 Pair Telco Male / Telco Female; Choose Any Length, Jacket (PVC or Plenum), and Degree of Cable Exit
735A Cable BNC Plug / BNC Plug
*SC-7154-1a Customize
735A Coaxial Cable 75 Ohm BNC Plug / BNC Plug; Choose Any Length, and Jacket (Standard PVC or Fire Rated Plenum)
More >
OEM Equivalents
PC
SCSI
Serial
Telco PBX
Featured:
Cat5e
Cat6
Cat6a
Cisco
Coaxial
Juniper
RJ21 & RJ21 Hydra
RS-530
T1
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Stonewall Cable, Inc. is committed to maintaining visitor privacy and secure transactions.
This privacy policy outlines how Stonewall Cable, Inc. collects, uses and protects information that you provide us. We are committed to ensuring your privacy. Information is protected with the highest security measures possible and your identity and information is not given to any third parties. If a situation should require that you provide data to be identified, we assure you it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.
All information is confidential. We do not sell, rent, or trade customer information with other companies.
We only require the information to fulfill the transaction and provide the highest quality customer service.
Transactions are conducted using the industry standard Transport Layer Security (TLS) protocol, the successor to Secure Socket Layer (SSL).
Credit card orders are processed in real-time using secure methods. Credit card information is not maintained on our server.
The secured server is maintained in a limited access location.
Changes to this policy will be posted here. Your business is important to us. If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy please:
E-mail sales@stonewallcable.com
Call 800-525-3303
Call 603-536-1601 (International)
Information We Collect
The following information we collect and retain for our records to help provide accurate, fast and reliable customer support and technical assistance:
Name (first and last)
Contact information (phone number, e-mail address, mailing address)
Other information (relevant to order history, industry, and company information)
What We do with the Information
Stonewall uses the information to:
Establish and update internal customer records
Improve products and services
Facilitate customer service requests
Facilitate technical service requests
Improve knowledge for future purchases
Send promotional and informational material (you can opt out at any time)
We will never distribute, sell or lease any of your information. We will never release any of your information unless we have your expressed consent or are required by law to do so. In accordance with the Data Protection Act of 1998, you may request details of your personal information. Please contact our customer service for additional information. If you believe your information is out of date or incorrect, it can be updated via My Account or you may call our customer service team for assistance.
Security Measures
Your information is never made available to the public. Our data is stored in a limited access location. To ensure unauthorized access, we have put in place advanced physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard your information.
About Cookies
Cookies are small electronic files which are stored on your computer's hard drive. Our system sends a request for your web browser to store this information. Cookies are used on nearly all websites that require a login, shopping cart or other data collection. Cookies are normal practice for all websites and no actions are needed on your part unless your browser doesn't automatically accept cookie requests. You can manage these settings in your browser's settings. These cookies allow our website to respond to you as an individual and keep your preferences and login credentials saved on your device, however, in no way do the cookies allow us access to information on your computer other than data saved in the cookie file. To enable cookies, see enable cookies.
You can view and delete stored cookies in your browser by visiting your settings or history.
Stonewall Cable, Inc.
126 Hawkensen Drive Rumney, NH 03266-3548
1-800-525-3303
sales@stonewallcable.comFax: 603-536-3240
Cage Code:
1PHQ9
NAICS Code:
334419
Line Card:
Download
Site Map
Contact Us
© 1997 - 2019 Stonewall Cable, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
*E-mail Address
*Password
Register |
Forgot Password?
Login
Close Window
Continue shopping
Back to top
